"Dear god, I've come to repent my sins..."
"Let your blood wash me clean For I'm...
I'm...
I'M.....
I'm a rotten girl....
I swore I'd never sin again
But my patience's running thin
The temptation flowing through my veins
I'm bounded by these shackles of shame.........
I promised I'd indulge no more
But my heart, I can't ignore
In my dreams they're turning up the heat
I'm a dirty, rotten girl
On lock, underneath the bleachers
Just watch! Look beyond the smoke and mirrors
Heartstruck?! Shun the nonbeliever!
Our operation would never be complete
Red hot, tension with each whisper
Snapshot! Quiet moans and muffled whimpers
Come on, can't you feel the fever
Rising up, Rising up to the sky?
As testaments echo, fear ignites beneath my skin
The lord sayeth “halt thy child, don’t give into sin”
It's driving me crazy
The urge to forsake thee
Yet, something shifts within this wicked bliss
I swore I'd never sin again
But my patience's running thin
Student council breathing down my neck
I wonder if they're hiding from me...?
Forbidden fruits before my eyes
And a taste that's so divine
My regrets rewriting history
I'm a sad, pathetic girl
Someone please tell me what to do...
Because, honestly I just can't stop!!!
I've been trying so hard and I can't stop!!
What would god think？！
and I know I'm supposed to be a good girl-
but- somehow I just can't control myself--
Everytime I see them...
touching skin to skin...
my- my mind goes-AUYHSAHDASASSA"
Could Eve be our idol? Could she lead us through the light?
We’d all be disciples of her lemon driven bite
Can somebody save me
The urge to forsake thee
Still, something shifts within this wicked bliss
The power resting in my hands
For my God has other plans
In salvation I can live my life
As an ordinary girl
I can't resist it anymore
Cause I smell slow burn galore
all the trauma from a cobblestone
could never beat the devil in me
An honest sinner 'till i die
What's the harm if i don't mind?
With the paddle that empowers me
I can live a sinful life